https://bestviva.net/privacy-policy/

BestViva Top MenuHomeAbout UsPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsDisclaimerContact Us Main MenuElectronicsSports & OutdoorsHealth & Personal CareAutomotiveHomeAbout UsPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsDisclaimerContact Us
ElectronicsSports & OutdoorsHealth & Personal CareAutomotivePrivacy PolicyHome›Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy for bestviva.netIf you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us here.At bestviva.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by bestviva.net and how it is used.Log FilesLike many other Web sites, bestviva.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.Cookies and Web Beaconsbestviva.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.Amazon Associates ProgramBestviva.net is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com. Amazon, the Amazon logo, AmazonSupply, and the AmazonSupply logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates. As an Amazon Associate we earn affiliate commissions from qualifying purchases.DoubleClick DART Cookie.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on bestviva.net. .:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to bestviva.net and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.htmlSome of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …. Google Adsense Commission Junction Clickbank Amazon Associates These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on bestviva.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. bestviva.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. bestviva.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.About the SiteBestViva team reads consumers’ reviews, examine their ranking and ranks the best 10 productsLatest PostsBest Window Air Conditioners in 2020By Lun SovannMay 7, 2020Best Stopwatches in 2020By Lun SovannMay 7, 2020Best Bicycle Floor Pumps for Cyclists in 2020By Lun SovannMay 7, 2020Best Wireless Routers in 2020By Lun SovannMay 2, 2020Best Gaming Mice in 2020By Lun SovannMay 2, 2020CategoriesAutomotive Baby Products Beauty Cell Phones & Accessories Clothing, Shoes & Jewelry Computers Electronics Health & Personal Care Home & Kitchen Industrial & Scientific Kitchen & Dining Musical Instruments Office Products Outdoor Recreation Patio, Lawn & Garden Pet Supplies Photography Supplies Sports & Outdoors Tools & Home Improvement Toys & GamesHomeAbout UsContact UsTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyDisclaimerCopyright © 2020 · BestViva
